Beth! We are waiting for you.
Beth! 我们在等你.
The phone is driving me crazy.
电话真让我发疯.
Let's unplug it. I'm starting.
咱们把插头拔了吧.我开始吃了.
Beth!
Coming.
来了.
Sorry.
对不起.
Hey, didn't you have a soccer game today?
Hey,今天你不是有足球赛吗?
What was the score?
比分如何?
Four to...
4比...
Tell them you are eating dinner and will call back later.
告诉他们你在吃饭, 过会儿再打给他们.
You see what I mean?
你明白我的意思吗?
Dad! It's for you.
爸爸!你的电话.
Sorry.
对不起.
The phone is driving me crazy.
这电话真让我发疯.
Mom, we should just turn on the answering machine.
妈妈,我们应该打开电话留言机.
I don't want to use it to screen calls.
我不想用电话留言来筛选电话.
I don't think it's right.
我认为这样做不妥.
If we're home, we should answer the phone.
如果我们在家,我们应该接电话.
But we're not screening calls.
但是我们并不是筛选电话.
We just don't want to be interrupted.
我们只是不想被打扰.
If we were eating out, the machine would be on.
如果我们在外面吃饭,电话留言机就会开着.
You have a point.
你说的有道理.
So, let's use it during meals or just during dinner.
那么,我们吃饭时就用电话留言吧 或只在吃晚饭时用.
Maybe.
也许吧.
Sorry. That was Joe.
对不起.刚才是Joe打来的.
What did he want?
他有什么事?
The phone is driving you crazy.
这电话让人发疯.
Nan! It's for you.
Nan!是你的电话.